Contact

kathy_bonser@ssmhc.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kathy-bonser-0b90491b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare Management Hospitals

Certifications

Nurse Executive Advanced (NEA-BC)

Kathy Bonser

Regional Vice President Nursing/CNO at SSM Heath-St. Louis Saint Louis, Missouri

Summary

Senior Nursing Executive with over 20 years leadership and management experience in health care. Highly motivated, transformational leader with proven record of engaging staff and partnering with physicians to achieve operational goals and objectives. Dedicated advocate for patient and staff safety with the ability to build solid, productive teams to drive process improvement and improve the clinical care of patients served. Champion for evidence based nursing practice and shared decision making to support nurses and empower them to oversee their professional practice by making decisions that impact their work.

Experience

SSM Heath-St. Louis
Regional Vice President Nursing/CNO
July 2016 - Present (4 years 1 month)
St. Louis

SSM Health DePaul Hospital-St. Louis Vice President Nursing/CNO April 2006 - Present (14 years 4 months) SSM Health DePaul Hospital St. Louis

SSM DePaul Health Center 14 years

Director Nursing 1998 - 2006 (8 years) SSM Health DePaul Hospital St. Louis

Nurse Manager Ambulatory Surgery/Endoscopy/PACU 1992 - 1998 (6 years) SSM Health Depaul Hospital St. Louis

Page 1 of 2

Education

Lindenwood University

Master of Science, Health Care Administration · (2005 - 2007)

Southeast Missour

Bachelor Of Science, Nursing · (1977 - 1981)